NAVELI BANERJEE

Email address: naveli.banerjee@gmail.com
Home phone: +91 8850520172

Mumbai, India

A graduate with a BA (Hons) in Finance Economics achieving a degree classification of higher 2:1 and have recently completed my post-graduate diploma in Economics and Financial Economics. I have gained the critical skills such as analytical, research, quantitative, accounting, computer, problem-solving and communication skills through my studies and work experiences. My goal is to build a career in the corporate setting, where I can get the opportunity to display my skills and develop them further by accepting challenges, which can help me to highly contribute to the organisation.

EDUCATION

University of Nottingham, UK: 2018 - 2019

Post Graduate Diploma: Financial Economics and Economics

Modules: Microeconomic Theory, Macroeconomic Theory, Econometric Theory, Econometric Data Analysis, Development Policy Analysis, Development Microeconomics, Economics of Corporate Finance and Principles of Accounting

Research Topic: The Impact of Agricultural Credits on Farm Production: A Case Study in India

Coventry University, UK: 2015 - 2018

Undergraduate study: Bachelor of Arts with Honours in Financial Economics

Accredited by the Chartered Association of Business Schools (CABS) and European Foundation for Management Development (EFMD)

Upper second class (2:1)

Modules: Mathematical techniques for Economists, Principles of Accountings, Current Issues in Applied Economics, Intermediate Economics, Quantitative Economics, Principles of Financial Investments and Basic Accounting, Applied Econometrics, Investment Analysis, Advanced Economic Issues, Advanced Economics Dissertation

Research Topic: Contribution of Islamic Banking to the Economic Growth of Malaysia

A Levels, English School of Fahaheel, Kuwait

International GCSE, English School of Fahaheel, Kuwait: Including Mathematics and English - First Language.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Quality Assurance in Lidl Headquarters UK – London, UK (January 2020 – March 2020)

- Investigated large volumes of customer complaints on products, conducted follow-ups with suppliers in a timely manner.
- Responded to the customers through emails and letters, managed complaint priority.
- Provided adequate responses to suppliers and correct action plans were implemented.
- Scanned multiple documents for additional information quickly and was successfully able to compare against other sources and internal database.
- Gained major expertise in Salesforce to implement the investigation process and responses into the system.

Marketing and Sales in Quantum Acquisition – London, UK (December 2019 – January 2020)

- Dealt with new and existing customers on daily basis to represent the company's clients to the public.
- Generated new customer base for the clients; worked towards collective team and individual targets.

Research, Finance and Data Management in Bespoke Connections – London, UK (September 2019 – November 2019)

- Worked alongside senior management to create/implement changes by using extensive research, presentation, data analysis and data visualisation skills to achieve positive business outcomes.
- Reviewed news, webs and relevant articles to conduct primary and secondary research and then quickly extracted and entered the information on Salesforce.
- Used Salesforce thoroughly to manage data and keep a track of all the operations, including creating campaigns and profiles.

Summer Analyst - Internship in Reliance Asset Reconstruction Company Limited - Mumbai, India

(August 2016 - September 2016)

- Examined the tendency of the NPA market in India and wrote a report on it.
- Displayed strong numerical and analytical skills.
- Developed my skill in advanced Excel and Word.
- The completion of assigned jobs within stipulated time proved my ability in time management.
- The opportunity to work within a group, instilled more confidence in my teamwork spirit and enhanced communication skills.

IT SKILLS

- Completing Tally ERP 9 Advanced Course Accounting, Inventory, GST, GTA, Banking, Payroll and TDS.
- Completion of SQL and Relational Databases 101
- Completion of Python for Data Science by IBM
- 6 months work experience in using Salesforce.
- Completed the ECDL Advanced Spreadsheet Microsoft Excel certificate programme.
- A year of experience in working with STATA for my post-graduate studies.
- Worked extensively with Gretyl, SPSS and Oxmetrics software throughout my education.

OTHER ACHIEVEMENTS

- Been a member of the Financial Trading Society at Coventry University
- Completed the Impetus Training Cultural Programme, offered by the centre for global engagement at Coventry University.
- Volunteered at Food for All Coventry, UK
- Volunteered for Breast Cancer Awareness and Philippines flood relief Kuwait City, Kuwait
- Language skills: English (fluent), Hindi (fluent), Bengali (intermediate) and Arabic (basic).

REFERENCES AVAILABLE ON REQUEST